<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>www-cloud</title>
    <link href="https://www-cloud.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www-cloud.github.io" />
    <updated>2021-01-24T00:57:15-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Stan Holmes</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www-cloud.github.io</id>

    <entry>
        <title>test</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Holmes</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www-cloud.github.io/test.html"/>
        <id>https://www-cloud.github.io/test.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-24T00:46:53-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    ok now
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>ok now</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Amazon Contact Number</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Holmes</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www-cloud.github.io/amazon-contact-number.html"/>
        <id>https://www-cloud.github.io/amazon-contact-number.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-24T00:56:10-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Francis Peak is providing reference below, when you need to get in touch with Amazon by phone. 1 (888) 280-4331 
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><a href="https://francispeak.com/">Francis Peak</a> is providing reference below, when you need to get in touch with Amazon by phone.  <br> 1 (888) 280-4331 </p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Prime Systems</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Holmes</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www-cloud.github.io/prime-systems.html"/>
        <id>https://www-cloud.github.io/prime-systems.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-24T00:56:10-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Francis Peak invites you to learn more about Prime Systems. Prime Systems was founded in June of 1990 by Keith R. Duncan. The company was only Keith and Delvin Read in the beginning years, Keith would sell the systems and Delvin would build them.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><a href="https://francispeak.com">Francis Peak</a> invites you to learn more about Prime Systems. <br><a href="http://primesystemsinc.com/">Prime Systems</a> was founded in June of 1990 by Keith R. Duncan. The company was only Keith and Delvin Read in the beginning years, Keith would sell the systems and Delvin would build them. Keith would deliver the systems and to this day the company still delivers the vast majority of systems built. </p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Sundays Off</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Holmes</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www-cloud.github.io/sundays-off.html"/>
        <id>https://www-cloud.github.io/sundays-off.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-24T00:57:15-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                     Sundays are different in many ways from the rest of the week. Francis Peak recognizes companies that close down for Sunday. It is great to be an employee of these companies. Following is a list of a few of such companies, let us know&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p>Sundays are different in many ways from the rest of the week. <a href="https://francispeak.com/">Francis Peak</a> recognizes companies that close down for Sunday. It is great to be an employee of these companies. Following is a list of a few of such companies, let us know of others. <br><br><a href="https://www.tabbank.com/">https://www.tabbank.com/</a> <br><a href="https://tannerclinic.com/">https://tannerclinic.com/</a> <br><a href="https://www.americafirst.com/">https://www.americafirst.com/</a> <br><a href="https://www.bowmansmarket.com/">https://www.bowmansmarket.com/</a> </p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- wp:paragraph --></p>
<p><!-- /wp:paragraph --></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Francis Peak - History</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Holmes</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www-cloud.github.io/francis-peak-history.html"/>
        <id>https://www-cloud.github.io/francis-peak-history.html</id>
            <category term="Utah"/>
            <category term="Morgan"/>
            <category term="Francis Peak"/>
            <category term="Davis"/>

        <updated>2021-01-24T00:56:10-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Francis Peak, Elevation 9,560 feet (2,910 m), was named in honor of an early pioneer, Esther Charlotte Emily Weisbrodt Francis, who contributed to the colonization of the Morgan Valley in Morgan county in Utah. One of the taller peaks of the Wasatch Range, Francis Peak&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><a href="https://francispeak.com">Francis Peak</a>, Elevation 9,560 feet (2,910 m), was named in honor of an early pioneer, Esther Charlotte Emily Weisbrodt Francis, who contributed to the colonization of the Morgan Valley in Morgan county in <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Utah">Utah</a>. One of the taller peaks of the Wasatch Range, <a href="https://francispeak.com">Francis Peak</a> is located on the border between Morgan and Davis counties, approximately 18 miles (29 km) north of Salt Lake City, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Utah">Utah</a>, United States.</p>
<p>The summit is accessible by hiking, biking, recreational vehicles, and automobile. Automobiles can access the peak via Skyline Drive in Bountiful and Farmington Canyon Road in Farmington. Camping sites, trails, small ponds, wildlife and great vistas are part of this rugged natural setting.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Privacy Policy</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Holmes</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www-cloud.github.io/privacy-policy.html"/>
        <id>https://www-cloud.github.io/privacy-policy.html</id>

        <updated>2021-01-24T00:56:10-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Who we areOur website address is: https://francispeak.com. When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <h2>Who we are</h2>
<p>Our website address is: https://francispeak.com.</p>
<h2>What personal data we collect and why we collect it</h2>
<h3>Comments</h3>
<p>When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.</p>
<p>An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.</p>
<h3>Media</h3>
<p>If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.</p>
<h3>Contact forms</h3>
<h3>Cookies</h3>
<p>If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.</p>
<p>If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.</p>
<p>When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.</p>
<p>If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.</p>
<h3>Embedded content from other websites</h3>
<p>Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.</p>
<p>These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.</p>
<h3>Analytics</h3>
<h2>Who we share your data with</h2>
<h2>How long we retain your data</h2>
<p>If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.</p>
<p>For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.</p>
<h2>What rights you have over your data</h2>
<p>If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.</p>
<h2>Where we send your data</h2>
<p>Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.</p>
<h2>Your contact information</h2>
<h2>Additional information</h2>
<h3>How we protect your data</h3>
<h3>What data breach procedures we have in place</h3>
<h3>What third parties we receive data from</h3>
<h3>What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data</h3>
<h3>Industry regulatory disclosure requirements</h3>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Web Code Help - great reference for Technology</title>
        <author>
            <name>Stan Holmes</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www-cloud.github.io/web-code-help-great-reference-for-technology.html"/>
        <id>https://www-cloud.github.io/web-code-help-great-reference-for-technology.html</id>
            <category term="website"/>
            <category term="Utah"/>
            <category term="Technology"/>

        <updated>2021-01-24T00:56:10-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    Web Code Help is a great reference for Technology.
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p><a href="https://webcodehelp.com">Web Code Help</a> is a great reference for Technology.</p>

            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
